[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "What is the collective mood at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "collective", "mood", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "I think it's a change of generations more than the difference of culture.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "change", "of", "generations", "more", "than", "the", "difference", "of", "culture", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard about this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "heard", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "I think gossiping is a bad thing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "gossiping", "is", "a", "bad", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Are you confident that you have President Obama's full hundred percent support?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "confident", "that", "you", "have", "President", "Obama", "'s", "full", "hundred", "percent", "support", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "You know, when I judge by his actions he really has shown friendship.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "when", "I", "judge", "by", "his", "actions", "he", "really", "has", "shown", "friendship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "I mean, how serious should we be taking your comments?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "how", "serious", "should", "we", "be", "taking", "your", "comments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Well, I don't think that this is a correct interpretation of what I have said.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "this", "is", "a", "correct", "interpretation", "of", "what", "I", "have", "said", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "When you have somebody in his position with his kind of power apparently are getting nearer and nearer to a nuclear capability, are you surprised that more leaders around the world are not making a more concerted effort to get rid of him, to enforce regime change?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "have", "somebody", "in", "his", "position", "with", "his", "kind", "of", "power", "apparently", "are", "getting", "nearer", "and", "nearer", "to", "a", "nuclear", "capability", ",", "are", "you", "surprised", "that", "more", "leaders", "around", "the", "world", "are", "not", "making", "a", "more", "concerted", "effort", "to", "get", "rid", "of", "him", ",", "to", "enforce", "regime", "change", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJR", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "I think in the beginning most of the leaders thought that it would take a longer period of time before they'll have a bomb.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "in", "the", "beginning", "most", "of", "the", "leaders", "thought", "that", "it", "would", "take", "a", "longer", "period", "of", "time", "before", "they", "'ll", "have", "a", "bomb", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Could you foresee a situation where Israel may take military action without the whole support of the United Nations or indeed America?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "foresee", "a", "situation", "where", "Israel", "may", "take", "military", "action", "without", "the", "whole", "support", "of", "the", "United", "Nations", "or", "indeed", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "CC", "RB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Israel fails to foresee what the world is doing.", "answer_tokens": ["Israel", "fails", "to", "foresee", "what", "the", "world", "is", "doing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United Nations"], "LOCATION": ["Israel", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "What is your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "I think they've created a mistake, but mistakes are being done by many people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'ve", "created", "a", "mistake", ",", "but", "mistakes", "are", "being", "done", "by", "many", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "What do you think he would have made of the fact that there is still no settlement with the Palestinians so long after he started this process?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "he", "would", "have", "made", "of", "the", "fact", "that", "there", "is", "still", "no", "settlement", "with", "the", "Palestinians", "so", "long", "after", "he", "started", "this", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "He would concentrate on this issue as the main topic.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "would", "concentrate", "on", "this", "issue", "as", "the", "main", "topic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "What is the definition of news in the modern age, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "definition", "of", "news", "in", "the", "modern", "age", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Oh, I think it's very clear.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "clear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard Engel"]}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Has it been exceptional?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "been", "exceptional", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "I see our chief foreign correspondent Richard Engel in our building when he's in this country.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "see", "our", "chief", "foreign", "correspondent", "Richard", "Engel", "in", "our", "building", "when", "he", "'s", "in", "this", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Tell me about that unique place that you have as a news anchor in America?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "about", "that", "unique", "place", "that", "you", "have", "as", "a", "news", "anchor", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "Well, first of all, and no false modesty here either.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "and", "no", "false", "modesty", "here", "either", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Are you a news adrenaline junkie?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "news", "adrenaline", "junkie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "It's the most disturbing story in so long that we've come across, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "most", "disturbing", "story", "in", "so", "long", "that", "we", "'ve", "come", "across", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Are you pleased with this new addition to the armory?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "pleased", "with", "this", "new", "addition", "to", "the", "armory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NBC News"], "PERSON": ["Nancy"]}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "What would you say to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "If a candidate walked into our offices with her academic training, with her travel, with her access and time around conversations at the highest levels with policy makers, with her business experience, with just her travel experience, we would sit down if their name was Nancy, and have a thorough conversation about coming to work for us at NBC News.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "a", "candidate", "walked", "into", "our", "offices", "with", "her", "academic", "training", ",", "with", "her", "travel", ",", "with", "her", "access", "and", "time", "around", "conversations", "at", "the", "highest", "levels", "with", "policy", "makers", ",", "with", "her", "business", "experience", ",", "with", "just", "her", "travel", "experience", ",", "we", "would", "sit", "down", "if", "their", "name", "was", "Nancy", ",", "and", "have", "a", "thorough", "conversation", "about", "coming", "to", "work", "for", "us", "at", "NBC", "News", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Have you struggled to sleep at night with the idea that any one of those might have been innocent?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "struggled", "to", "sleep", "at", "night", "with", "the", "idea", "that", "any", "one", "of", "those", "might", "have", "been", "innocent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "No, sir, I've never struggled with that at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "sir", ",", "I", "'ve", "never", "struggled", "with", "that", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "We are in extraordinary times, aren't we?", "question_tokens": ["We", "are", "in", "extraordinary", "times", ",", "are", "n't", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "We are.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "What do you think's gone wrong with the American business model?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "'s", "gone", "wrong", "with", "the", "American", "business", "model", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Well, in my -- thank you for saying that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "my", "--", "thank", "you", "for", "saying", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "You like this kind of stuff, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "like", "this", "kind", "of", "stuff", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Well, I -- I'm -- I don't -- I never know what to say about this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "I", "'m", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "never", "know", "what", "to", "say", "about", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "I'm told that one of your numerous comedic talents is you do a very good impression of me?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "told", "that", "one", "of", "your", "numerous", "comedic", "talents", "is", "you", "do", "a", "very", "good", "impression", "of", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Just my favorite thing about you -- in addition to the title graphic which shows you in that room with so many dust particles.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "my", "favorite", "thing", "about", "you", "--", "in", "addition", "to", "the", "title", "graphic", "which", "shows", "you", "in", "that", "room", "with", "so", "many", "dust", "particles", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "But how many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Once and I remain there.", "answer_tokens": ["Once", "and", "I", "remain", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tom Brokaw"]}, "docId": "111114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", ",", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "What has been the greatest moment of your life, of all the things you've been involved with, that you witnessed, everything?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "been", "the", "greatest", "moment", "of", "your", "life", ",", "of", "all", "the", "things", "you", "'ve", "been", "involved", "with", ",", "that", "you", "witnessed", ",", "everything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "If we're leaving aside marriage and birth of children and things like that, I would have to say, because it has defined me and it gives me the job title on my business card -- I would have to say taking this job when Tom Brokaw stepped down, because it was so unlikely, because of my very modest circumstances growing up, dropping out of school, kicking around and really not showing any promise.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "we", "'re", "leaving", "aside", "marriage", "and", "birth", "of", "children", "and", "things", "like", "that", ",", "I", "would", "have", "to", "say", ",", "because", "it", "has", "defined", "me", "and", "it", "gives", "me", "the", "job", "title", "on", "my", "business", "card", "--", "I", "would", "have", "to", "say", "taking", "this", "job", "when", "Tom", "Brokaw", "stepped", "down", ",", "because", "it", "was", "so", "unlikely", ",", "because", "of", "my", "very", "modest", "circumstances", "growing", "up", ",", "dropping", "out", "of", "school", ",", "kicking", "around", "and", "really", "not", "showing", "any", "promise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]